{
	"test": [
		{
			"number": 1,
			"question": "Which branch of the federal government can veto legislation?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"The President",
				"The US House of Representatives",
				"The US Senate",
				"The US Supreme Court"
			],
			"answer": "The President"
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"question": "Review the statement below: \n\n'On D-Day, June 6, 1944, Allied forces sustained more than 10,000 casualties.' \n\nThis statement is best classified as:",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"An opinion",
				"A scientific conclusion",
				"A fact",
				"An inference"
			],
			"answer": "A fact"
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"question": "Based on this excerpt, what was Washington's opinion of foreign alliances?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_1",
			"answers": [
				"Permanent alliances are appropriate for emergency situations.",
				"No new agreements should be made, and existing agreements should not be honored.",
				"No permanent foreign alliances should be made.",
				"Agreements should be extended only if they will promote freedom and democracy abroad."
			],
			"answer": "No permanent foreign alliances should be made."
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"question": "Which of the following programs was designed to help people of all income levels?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_2",
			"answers": [
				"Housing and Urban Development Act",
				"Higher Education Act",
				"Medicare",
				"Medicaid"
			],
			"answer": "Medicare"
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"question": "According to the excerpt, a proposal for amending the Constitution is considered valid when it is:",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_3",
			"answers": [
				"proposed by 2/3 of the Senate.",
				"proposed by 2/3 of each chamber of Congress.",
				"proposed by 3/4 of the state legislatures.",
				"proposed by 3/4 of each chamber of Congress."
			],
			"answer": "proposed by 2/3 of each chamber of Congress."
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"question": "Which of the following statements is NOT true about this graph?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_4",
			"answers": [
				"The equilibrium price is less than 3.",
				"The quantity demanded will increase with lower prices.",
				"A surplus will occur if 20 units are supplied at a price of 4.50.",
				"The quantity supplied will increase with lower prices."
			],
			"answer": "The quantity supplied will increase with lower prices."
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"question": "Which of the following best describes the philosophy of the Libertarian political party?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"Ecological wisdom, social justice, grassroots democracy, and peace.",
				"Fiscal conservatism and social liberalism.",
				"Principles found in the U.S. Declaration of Independence, and social policies taken from the Bible.",
				"Economic liberalism, fiscal conservatism, and social conservatism."
			],
			"answer": "Fiscal conservatism and social liberalism."
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"question": "Which of these conclusions is supported by this graph?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_5",
			"answers": [
				"The statutory debt limit helps reduce debt.",
				"Total debt will exceed $18 Trillion in a few years.",
				"Total debt has increased during the terms of the last 5 presidents.",
				"Current levels of debt are not sustainable."
			],
			"answer": "Total debt has increased during the terms of the last 5 presidents."
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"question": "Based on this excerpt, the Supreme Court found all of the following faults with segregation in schools EXCEPT:",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_6",
			"answers": [
				"Slows mental development.",
				"Reduces motivation to learn.",
				"Denotes inferiority.",
				"Provides fewer resources to minority schools."
			],
			"answer": "Provides fewer resources to minority schools."
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"question": "Based on this excerpt, what you can you infer about Susan B. Anthony?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_3_7",
			"answers": [
				"She worked closely with Elizabeth Cady Stanton.",
				"She was not found guilty of any crime.",
				"She was a Constitutional lawyer.",
				"She was arrested for voting because of her gender."
			],
			"answer": "She was arrested for voting because of her gender."
		}
	]
}
